

Charlie Rios Pujado

Date of birth: 12/03/1999
Nationality: Spanish

CONTACT

9

Barcelona 08038 Barcelona, Spain (**Home**)



xarlizard@outlook.com



http://Charlie.icu



linkedin.com/in/Charlie-rios



ABOUT ME

Multi-role profile in IT.

Programmer oriented to web development, from Full-Stack programming to Layout and Web positioning.

IT specialist/manager with experience in systems/server administration oriented to B2B (Business to business) services.

Committed, proactive and constantly learning.

WORK EXPERIENCE

12/2022 - 09/2024 Ibiza (remote), Spain

FullStack Web Developer Pixelimperium / Freelance

Web Developer

- Front-end (HTML/CSS/Javascript/Typescript/React/Nextjs) and Back-end(Nodejs/Python)
- eCommerce deployment and management through WordPress, PrestaShop and Shopify
- UI/UX design, SQL databases, REST, GIT, Software Testing, API's
- Blockchain & Web3 Technology (Solidity)

05/2022 - 09/2022 Molins De Rei, Spain

Developer & IT Consultant DR Finantrust, S.L.

Finance-oriented business. Software for trading on currency/stocks market.

05/2020 - 05/2022 Hospitalet de Llobregat, Spain

IT Team Manager & Software Developer Businessprinter, S.L.

IT services company B2B (BusinessToBusiness)

- Head of the IT department and technicians team.
- Systems, servers & networks setup/management/troubleshooting.
- Apps/Web designing, development and management.

05/2017 - 05/2020 Cornellà, Spain

System Admin (L2) MagnumObject,S.L.

IT services & components company.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

09/2019 - 06/2020 Barcelona, Spain

 FP Grado Superior DAW (Web Apps Development) IOC (Institut Obert de Catalunya)

09/2017 - 06/2019 Barcelona, Spain

FP Grado Superior DAM (Multiplatform Apps Development) Salesi ans de Sarrià

09/2015 - 06/2017 Barcelona, Spain

Baccalaureate in Science/Technology Institut Proa (Proa's Senior Highschool)

04/2024 - 06/2024 Helsinki, Finland

Fullstack Open Developer University of Helsinki

Website https://www.helsinki.fi/en

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Spanish | Catalan | English **OTHER LANGUAGE(S):** Japanese | French | Italian